<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Links | ComnGood</title>
    <link>https://links.comngood.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Links | ComnGood</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://links.comngood.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dar Agency</title>
      <link>https://links.comngood.org/all/dar-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://links.comngood.org/all/dar-agency/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exodus 90</title>
      <link>https://links.comngood.org/all/exodus-90/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://links.comngood.org/all/exodus-90/</guid>
      <description>Exodus 90 is all about freedom. Why? Because without freedom, we cannot love as we ought. It’s about our wives, children, parishes and friends who suffer when we’re not at our best. The goal is to achieve the freedom necessary to fully engage the love of God and the love of neighbor. Exodus 90 is based on a challenging 90-day period of purification, a dying to self, which is supported by a fraternity of like-minded men for greater interior freedom and, eventually, a more purified and selfless love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fight the New Drug</title>
      <link>https://links.comngood.org/all/fight-the-new-drug/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://links.comngood.org/all/fight-the-new-drug/</guid>
      <description>Fight the New Drug is a non-religious and non-legislative organization that exists to provide individuals the opportunity to make an informed decision regarding pornography by raising awareness on its harmful effects using only science, facts, and personal accounts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Solidarity International</title>
      <link>https://links.comngood.org/all/human-solidarity-international/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://links.comngood.org/all/human-solidarity-international/</guid>
      <description>Somos un centro de estudios interdisciplinario, que se ha propuesto contribuir a la construcción del bien común de nuestras sociedades mediante el desarrollo de pensamiento y promoción de la dignidad de la persona humana y sus derechos.
Queremos impactar en el desarrollo de políticas públicas y en las condiciones sociales, jurídicas, políticas y económicas de nuestras comunidades para que estas sean propicias para el desarrollo integral de cada persona humana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pints With Aquinas</title>
      <link>https://links.comngood.org/all/pints-with-aquinas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://links.comngood.org/all/pints-with-aquinas/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a podcast with Matt Fradd!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Population Research Institute</title>
      <link>https://links.comngood.org/all/population-research-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://links.comngood.org/all/population-research-institute/</guid>
      <description>The Population Research Institute is a (501c3) non-profit research organization whose core values hold that people are the world’s greatest resource. PRI’s goals are to educate on this premise, to expose the myth of overpopulation, and to expose human rights abuses committed in population control programs. Our growing, global network of pro-life groups spans over 80 countries.
We pledge to:
Debunk the myth of overpopulation, which cheapens human life and paves the way for abusive population control programs</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>